Leach, W. Barton (Walter Barton), 1900 -1971. Papers, 1920-1971: Finding Aid.
Papers, 1920-1971.
- CONTINGENT II
  - HARVARD MISCELLANY
    - Harvard Law School: 1948 - 1949 Professorship of Legal Education, 66-7
    - Harvard Law School: Programmed Instruction 1963, 66-8
  - AIR FORCE
    - Air Force - Office of Information 1956 - 1957, 66-9
    - Air University: Command and Staff College 1957 - 1959, 66-10
    - Air University: Maxwell Air Force Base 1958 - 1966, 66-11
    - Air University Quarterly Review, 66-12
    - Martin, Irene 1962, 66-13
    - Shelburne, James C. (Dr.) 1954 - 1960, 66-14